Contact

+918802150730 (Mobile) gargrsb@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rsbgarg (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Java

С

JavaScript

Languages

English

French

Hindi

Rishabh Garg

Senior Software Engineer | 5+ years Full Stack experience | Java, JavaScript, Mongo | BITS PILANI | Looking For New Opportunities New Delhi Area, India

Summary

I'm a Software Engineer with more than 5 years of work experience ranging from startups to large enterprises. Through this period I have developed high scale systems reaching more than 1 Billion devices that consume data entries at a rate of 1M/sec, enterprise e-commerce applications used by Fortune 500 companies, and fiddled with mobile app development amongst other things.

Looking out for new challenges with love for problem-solving, learning new technologies, and creating seamless user experiences.

Experience

CleverTap

3 years 1 month

Engineering Team Lead

May 2019 - Present (1 year 3 months)

Mumbai, Maharashtra

Developer

July 2017 - April 2019 (1 year 10 months)

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

The 15th joiner of the Engineering Team, which has grown to 100. Worked across all phases of the development cycle, solved customer-centric use cases, resolved on-call issues, and led projects to deliver amazing features.

SAP Labs India Software Engineer July 2015 - June 2017 (2 years) Bengaluru, Karnataka

Nagarro Senior Software Engineer July 2014 - June 2017 (3 years)

Gurgaon, India

Worked as a member of team creating the E-Commerce platform of multiple retail chains. Responsible for developing the custom Product detailing, listing, search WCMS components, recommendation based and time based offer components, account and billing components, checkout flows and Omnichannel use cases using JAVA, Spring , MYSQL , JavaScript , HTML and CSS

Involved in developing the B2C Scenario of Integrating SAP CRM backend to the Hybris Commerce Suite using Hybris Datahub developed using JAVA Spring, JSP, JavaScript and XML.

Developed the extension of Hybris Commerce responsible for providing the recommendations from Product Recommendation Intelligence and Offer Recommendation Intelligence services of Hybris Marketing using ODATA

Technologies Used: Java, Hybris, JSP, Ant, Spring, ODATA, jQuery, JavaScript, HTML.

Value Edge Research Software Development Intern January 2014 - June 2014 (6 months)

Developed Native iOS applications and a cross-platform PhoneGap based application. Also, created an OTA(Over-The-Air) platform for distribution of iOS applications using 'itms-services'.

Tech Stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Cordova, Objective-C, PHP.

Education

Birla Institute of Technology and Science

Bachelor of Engineering (B.E.) (Hons.), Computer Science · (2010 - 2014)

Activity

06/22/2020, Rishabh Garg added candidate to Senior Software Engineer